asperasoft.com 2014-12-22

# Privacy Policy l Aspera

**_Last Updated October 9, 2012_**

Aspera is committed to respecting your privacy. This general Privacy Policy sets forth the privacy principles that Aspera follows with respect to personal information collected from Aspera’s corporate website (www.asperasoft.com); support website (support@asperasoft.com); and cloud website (cloud.asperasoft.com); direct marketing campaigns, which may be conducted by telephone or email; at events hosted or attended by Aspera; or in the course of other similar marketing activities. The term “ **Personal Information** ” includes any information that enables you to be identified, such as your name, physical address, email address or phone number. This policy is part of the Terms of Use of Aspera’s website and subject to all its terms. Aspera reserves the right to update this policy from time to-time and will notify you of any new privacy policies by posting them on Aspera’s websites. We encourage you to check our websites frequently for any such notices. 

## Information Collected

#### Personal Information

Certain data and services provided through Aspera’s website require registration where Personal Information is collected. Registration and the provision of Personal Information are voluntary. These areas may also be password protected. If you do not want Aspera to use your Personal Information in the manner described below, do not register with Aspera. By providing Aspera your Personal Information you expressly agree to the terms of this policy. 

#### Cookies

Cookies are unique identifiers that are transferred to your device to enable Aspera’s systems to recognize your device for general web analytics and in order for Aspera to better serve you with more tailored information when you return to the website. Cookies do not identify you; unless you provide Aspera with your Personal Information you will remain anonymous. You can set most browsers to tell you when you are sent a cookie and to refuse to receive it. 

## Use and Dissemination of Personal Information

#### Use of Personal Information

If you have registered with Aspera either online, in paper form, or over the telephone or have provided Personal Information to Aspera by other means, Aspera uses this information to (i) contact you with customized marketing information by telephone, mail, online-download, or email or (ii) offer you seminars or webinars you may find of interest. Electronic communications will include an “unsubscribe” feature that will allow you to unregister from future communications. 

#### Transfer of Personal Information to Aspera Affiliates

Aspera may disclosure your Personal Information to its affiliates which may be located outside of the United States. 

#### Sharing of Personal Information with Third Parties

Unless Aspera otherwise informs you, Aspera does not sell or rent your Personal Information to any third parties. Aspera may share your personal data with third parties Aspera uses to implement its marketing communications. It may also share your Personal Information with third parties involved in joint marketing partnerships, seminars, webinars, or similar offerings. These third parties may be located outside of the United States. 

## Security

#### Security of Personal Information

Aspera undertakes commercially reasonable precautions to protect Personal Information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. Despite these precautions, resolute hackers may wrongfully gain access to your Personal Information. Although such unauthorized access is unlikely, Aspera wants to inform you of this risk and advise you that Aspera is not liable for any damages caused by such unauthorized access. 

#### Third Party Sites

This policy only addresses your activities from Aspera servers. Other sites (including those that Aspera links to) may have their own policies, which Aspera does not control. 

**support@asperasoft.com**

Aspera uses a third party hosted system for customer facing knowledge base and ticketing system.  This provider’s privacy policy is found at <http://www.zendesk.com/company/privacy#cookies-policy>.
